to
live like say welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God had written for
the whole world to keep brother
Julius and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage thou shall
have no other gods before me thou shall
not make unto the any Graven image or
any likeness of anything that is in
heaven above or that is in the earth
beneath or that is in the water under
the Earth thou shallal Not Bow Down
thyself to them nor serve them for I the
Lord thy God am a jealous God visiting
the iniquity of the fathers upon the
children unto the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me and
showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord would not
hold him Guiltless that taketh his name
in vain remember the Sabbath day to keep
it holy six days shall thou labor and do
all thy work but the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God in it thou
shall not do any work thou nor thy son
nor thy daughter thy man servant nor thy
maid servant nor thy cattle nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates for in
six days the Lord made Heaven and Earth
the sea and all there in them is and
rested the seventh day wherefore the
Lord blessed the Sabbath day and
hallowed it honor thy father and thy
mother that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee Thou shalt not kill thou shall not
commit adultery Thou shalt not steal
thou shallal not bear false witness
against thy neighbor thou shallal not
cover thy neighbor's house thou shallal
not cover thy neighbor's wife nor his
man's servant nor his maid servant nor
his Ox nor his ass nor anything that is
thy neighbors our scripture reading came
from Exodus 20: 1-17 may the Lord add a
blessing to the reading of his holy word
in Jesus name we pray and give thanks
amen amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time keep in mind that
all oy questions will not be answered
and all long scripture questions will
not be answered for time sake but we may
be able to point you in the direction of
a DVD or a CD that you can purchase by
calling the office so please be as
direct as possible with your questions
so we can be as direct as possible with
our answers out of the King James Bible
no other Bibles will be acknowledged on
this program also keep in mind that this
is a live stream and you may begin to
send in your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life and we asking that you keep your
questions to a two
scripture maximum but let me introduce
you to family that's on the panel this
evening we got brother Dre good evening
brother Julius good evening everybody
brother Jerome Grace and peace brother
James good evening grace and peace
everyone can you hear me well yes we
hear you well welcome brother and glad
to have you thank you sister Deborah
good
evening and we have sister Casey
engineering for us the guest caller is
with us and I'm brother Cornell sister
deil let begin with our first question
of the evening yes there are several
held over questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's Q&A so by Iran Israel asks is
there any significance to son that's Su
n being capitalized in Malachi 4 verse
two all right Malachi 4 and two the
significance of su being capitalized
brother Julius share some light brother
James let's go to that Malachi 4 but we
going to do we going to do this we going
to set this up by reading verse one and
then verse two m 4 verse1 and verse2
this is a typographical error instead of
spell instead of it being spelled s n it
is instead of spell s o n It's s u n
that's a typographical error how do I
know pick it up at verse one go ahead
let's look at who we talking about go
ahead for behold the day cometh that
shall burn as an oven and all the proud
yay and all that do wickedly shall be
stubbl and the day that cometh shall
burn them up sayeth the Lord of hosts
that it shall leave them neither root
nor Branch this is the beut of Prophecy
go ahead who we talking about go ahead
but unto you that fear my name shall the
son of righteousness arise with healing
in his wings so this is personifying
this is personifying a being not the Sun
that shine but this is none other than
the Lord Jesus you heard about the
Wicked at verse one now you going to now
you're hearing about the righteous
judgment the Judgment of the righteous
at verse two but unto you that fear my
name shall the son of righteousness
arise go ahead and and and ye shall go
forth and grow up as calves of the stall
so this is none other than Jesus the
spirit of the Lord spoke to Malachi but
let's go one other place let's go to
Second Chronicles 23 brother brother
James 2 Chronicles
23 let's look at it from from another
point of view second
Chronicle
23 okay we going read verse three and uh
verse two to 4 when you get it go ahead
and they went about in Judah second I'm
sorry 2 Samuel I'm sorry second Samuel
23 second Samuel okay 2 Samuel 23 pardon
me second Samuel
23 and pick it up at verse two okay
the spirit of the Lord spake by me and
his word was in my tongue what did he
say the god of Israel said the rock of
Israel spake to me he that ruleth over
men must be just ruling in the fear of
God go ahead one more and he shall be as
the light of the morning when the sun
riseth even a morning without clouds as
the tender grass springeth out of the
Earth by clear sh
after rain so it's the Bible speak
metaphorically but you got to understand
in Malachi it's talking about the sun
which is Jesus the Christ that's all I
got all right like to thank you brother
Julius for straightening that out Su n
versus s o n hope that answers your
question as we move on to our next one
moving on Tom Mara Williams asks is it
okay to eat pink salmon or tuna from the
can sure it's okay long as they have fs
and scales let's go into Leviticus the
11th chapter Leviticus
11 and also it's wise for you to make
sure that you read your can because they
starting to mix fish in together
now so but let's read about um the
salmon and the tuna that you asked about
Leviticus 11
and let's pick it up at that verse one
and then we go skip down to verse nine
go ahead my brother and the Lord spake
unto Moses and to Aaron saying unto them
all right so this the Lord and He
speaking out what it is that he want
done verse nine these shall ye eat of
all that are in the waters whatsoever
hath fins and scales in the waters in
the seas and in the rivers them shall ye
eat oh so whatever have fs and scales
whatever fish that has Fin and scales
that's in the waters in the rivers or in
the Seas you can eat go ahead brother
and all that have not fins and scales in
the seas and in the rivers of all that
move in the waters and of any living
thing which is in the waters they shall
be an abomination unto you so if it does
not have fins and scales in the seas and
the rivers and the waters you cannot eat
that because it is an Abomination unto
you verse
11 they shall be even an Abomination
unto you ye shall not eat of their flesh
but ye shall have their carcasses shall
have their carcasses in
Abomination one more verse whatsoever ha
no FS nor scales in the waters that
shall be an Abomination unto you so the
salmon and the tuna that's in the seas
and the waters and the rivers they have
fins and scales you are allowed to eat
those but make sure like I said that
whenever you buy your fish that you read
the package because they starting to mix
fish in together now and if it say
salmon and catfish mixed in together you
cannot eat that because catfish does not
have fins and
sces in addition to that brother Cornel
uh it is also clean it is also precooked
and
processed all right yep so we hope that
that helped to share some light on that
question for you as we continue to move
on yes the time is
7:45 I Chuck woar asks does Exodus 20
verse5 override
Ezekiel 18
1-4 and verses 18- 20 did the Lord later
make an exception to that initial law in
Exodus 20 at a later time saying that
Moses came before
Ezekiel all right quite a bit in that
question brother Dre what you say yeah
let's look at that let's go to Exodus 20
and read verse five
we'll read the Ezekiel
pce Thou shalt not bow down thyself to
them nor serve them for I the Lord thy
God am a jealous God visiting the
iniquity of the fathers upon the
children unto the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me now keep
that in mind because he said he's going
to visit the iniquity of the fathers
right upon the to the third and the
fourth generation and we're going to see
that happen and that actually
happened where we talking about during
Moses's
time so but let's go to that Ezekiel
passage now Ezekiel
18 and start at verse one I think he
said verse one to four okay verse one to
four go ahead when you get it James the
word of the Lord came unto me again
saying what mean ye that ye use this
proverb concerning the land of Israel
saying the fathers have eaten sour
grapes and the children's teeth are set
on edge as I live sayeth the Lord God ye
shall not have occasion anymore to use
this proverb in Israel behold All Souls
are mine as the soul of the father so
also the soul of the son is mine
the soul that sinth it shall die so the
the children this proverb that the
fathers eaten sour grapes they didn't
done wrong and the children's teeth are
set on edge he's saying what mean that
proverb he said but the soul that sinth
it shall die now skip down to verse 18
verse 18 and read to 20 okay as for his
father because his cruy oppressed
spoiled his brother by violence and did
that which is not good among his people
Lo even he shall die in his
iniquity yet say ye why doeth not the
son beare the iniquity of the father
when the son have done that which is
lawful and right and have kept all my
statutes and have done them he shall
surely live the soul that sinth it shall
shall die the son the son shall not bear
the iniquity of the father neither shall
the father bear the iniquity of the son
the righteousness of the righteous shall
be upon him and the wickedness of the
wicked shall be upon H so that is plain
but what we're talking about in Exodus
now let's go back to numbers and look at
what Israel did during this time during
the time and the effect that it had on
each of them let's go to numbers 14 and
we going to start at verse 26 numbers 14
and 26 go ahead brother when you get
it and the Lord spake unto Moses and
unto Aaron saying how long shall I bear
with the this evil congregation which
murmur against me I have heard the
murmurings of the children of Israel
which they murmur against me say unto
them as truly as I live sayeth the Lord
as ye have spoken in my ears so will I
do to
you your carcasses shall fall in the
wilderness and all that were numbered of
you according to your whole number from
20 years old and upward which have
murmured against me now notice it says
from 20 years old and upward those that
against them now what happened to the
ones that was 20 years and under let's
skip down to verse
33 go ahead and your children shall
wander in the wilderness 40 years and
bear your whoredoms until your carcasses
be wasted in the wilderness so Israel
the children was affected by what the
fathers did but keep going brother go go
ahead after the number of the days in
which he searched the land even 40 days
each day for a year shall ye bear your
iniquities even 40 years and ye shall
know my breach of
Promise that's right go ahead I the Lord
have said I will surely do it unto all
this evil congregation that all gathered
together against me in this wilderness
they shall be consumed and they sh and
there they shall die except for those
that were 20 years and under and those
were the direct children of those
fathers that sin that you're reading
about in Exodus 20 and5 it affected them
but they didn't pay for what they did
now the Lord they made a golden Cal but
the Lord showed Mercy because the Lord
can show Mercy on whom he will show
mercy and whom he judge he will
judge but what he said in in in Ezekiel
18 he's letting you know that the
children are not going to pay for the
fathers the soul that sinth it shall die
so I I hope that helps there's a little
bit more but that's how I'mma leave it
right there
yeah brother everybody from 19 and down
they survived that falling in the
wilderness right fact matter of fact I
gotta go ahead now Cornell let's go to
numbers 32 and read verses 11 and 12 and
13 that's it 321 and 12 yeah okay and
and uh 13 read that when you get there
brother okay surely none of the men that
came up out of egyp
from 20 years old and upward shall see
the land which I swear unto Abraham unto
Isaac and unto Jacob because they have
not wholly followed me save Caleb the
son of of jeith the kenite and Joshua
the son of nun for they have wholly
followed the Lord those were the two
exceptions because they followed the
Lord but besides them 20 years and
upward they didn't see it because of
what they did now read 13 brother and
the Lord's anger was kindled against
Israel and he made them wander in the
wilderness 40 years until all the
generation that had done evil in the
sight of the Lord was
consumed okay so again I hope that that
helps that's all I got cor now all right
thank you for that brother hope that a
answer their question sister Deborah
next one yes time
7:53 Valencia asked in Matthew 25
verse4 when the man gave his servants
the five talents and so on were they to
bring people into the Lord or do good
works brother Julius share some light
the answer is yes they are they were to
bring that's that's a parable about uh
the gifts that God give you the wisdom
knowledge and understanding and what you
do with that with those uh with those
gifts let's go to Matthew 25 and read
that 14 brother
James remember this is a parable go
ahead for the Kingdom of Heaven is as a
man traveling into a far country who
called his own servants and delivered
unto them his Goods 15 go ahead and unto
one he gave five talents to another and
to another one oh I'm sorry to another
two and to another one to every man
according to his several ability and
straightway took his journey Verse
18 but he that had received one went and
digged into the Earth and H and hid his
Lord's money yeah but just talking this
is talking about the gifts that God give
you the uh wi of knowledge and
understanding where you are able to
bring people to Christ and use it to
bring people to Christ but tell you what
I'm talking about let's get right to the
point if you not if you don't bring
people to to God look what he gonna do
at verse
30 and cast ye the unprofitable servant
into outer Darkness there shall be
weeping and nashing of teeth because you
didn't take what God gave you and you
didn't bring people to him and he
equipped you to do that that's all I got
anybody want to ask
yeah I want to throw something in real
quick everybody everybody tent is
different yes your talent sing praises
to the Lord you do that somebody else's
Talent might be prophesying somebody
else's Talent might be evangelizing
somebody else Talent might be uh going
out and feeding the poor in other words
you work in the Lord's Vineyard reason
I'm saying that is because you get
people say I talk but nobody come that
mean that I'm going to get not going to
get rewarded no you planted a
seed so you stay in the Lord your talent
might not be to bring masses of people
your talent might be just to show people
how gracious a servant of God is and
they want to be a
servant all I have to say Amen thank you
gu call all right thank you for that
hope that answered their question as we
move on yes TX Domino says in Psalms
55:14 is this David referring to a
friend when it states we took sweet
counsel together or Jesus referring to
God because this verse was used as to
show there are two Gods Jesus and the
father taking counsel
together all right your second part of
that question there is on point then the
first part was Jesus referring to god
let's go and read that brother because
this was Jesus speaking by the mouth of
David so let's go into that Psalms
55 Psalms
55 and pick it up at verse 12 because
this was Jesus here speaking about the
father go ahead for it was not an enemy
that reproached me then I could have
borne it neither was it he that hated me
that did magnify himself against me then
I would have him have hid myself from
him yes but it but it was thou a man my
equal my guide and my
acquaintance we took sweet counsel
together and walked into the house of
God in company so this is Jesus talking
about the father here when he said we
took sweet counsel together and walked
un to the house of God in company so
side by side decisions was made about
this Earth the coming of the son dying
for the sins and this evil man that
don't like to serve him so they did take
sweet counsel together and this was the
Jesus speaking to the father now let's
just go into uh Isaiah 57 right quick
Isaiah 57
and let's pick up the godhead right here
that there's only
two Isaiah
57 and pick it up at that verse 15 for
me when you get there because this is
talking about Jesus and the father right
here also go ahead for thus saith the
high and lofty one that inhabiteth
eternity whose name is Holy yeah I I
dwell in the high and holy holy place
with him also that is of a contrite and
humble Spirit to ret to revive the
spirit of the humble and revive the
heart of the contrite on yeah so this is
Jesus and the father here that he's
speaking about right here when he say
that he dwells also with him that is of
a humble and contr spirit so there's
only two Thrones in heaven the father's
on one and Jesus the son is on the other
so yeah this was uh the Father and Son
taking sweet counsel
together that's all I
got first in Isaiah 53rd chapter to tell
you talk about Jesus with his strike
real heal and it says yet uh uh Thou
made his soul an offer for sin who made
his off a soul and off for sin the
father that's why he said wasn't that
Afflicted me
okay that's that's correct all right
thank you for that addition hope that
answered your question there as we
continue to move on moving on they
should a love it ass can you visit the
hospital on the Sabbath
day brother Dre when you got the sick at
the hospital can you go pay them a visit
on the Sabbath day absolutely uh let's
go to James the first chapter and we're
gonna read verse 27 James 1 and 27 James
read it when you get
there P religion and undefiled before
God and the father is this to visit the
fatherless and widows in their
Affliction and to keep himself unspotted
from the world oh yeah people are in
their Affliction you can visit them I
don't see nothing wrong with that now
let's go over to uh James the 5th
chapter
James 5 and we gon to read verse
14 is any sick among you let him call
for the Elders of the church and let
them pray over him anointing him with
oil in the name of the
Lord yeah oh last one one last place
Mark 3 you know Jesus came in there was
a man with a withered hand and it was on
the Sabbath day and the Pharisees sought
to accuse him so start at verse one Mark
3 And1 go ahead when you get
it and he entered again into the
synagogue and there was a man there
which had a withered hand and they
watched him whether he would heal him on
the Sabbath day that they might accuse
him and he said unto the man which had
the withered hand stand forth and he
said unto them
it is is it lawful to do good on the
Sabbath days or to do evil to save life
or to kill but they held their peace
because it is lawful to do good on the
Sabbath and if somebody is sick and you
visit them you doing them something good
I hope that that
helps yes sir indeed thank you brother
because we know sickness is everywhere
from one end clean to the
thank you brother for that as we
continue to move on to the next question
next question sister Israel ask why do
people say bless you after you
sneeze brother juli is after somebody go
H Che why do they bless them after they
do that that is uh because they they
don't understand that that is folklore
and
tradition folklore and tradition some
people for a variety of reasons some
people say it's because
uh uh your heart sto you know uh some
people got many different reasons some
people say it in German gazuntite which
means good health it don't mean God
bless you it means good health but the
bottom line is it is tradition has
nothing to do with the word of
God yep all right thank you for that
brother as we move on to our next one
moving on little mama Hayes asks is
Mystery Babylon America or is it the
Roman Catholic
Church mystery Babylon or the Roman
Catholic Church brother Jerome Shar some
light no it's not America it it is the
Roman Catholic church and uh they rid
and uh that church is riding on on this
beach that we going to read about in
this Revelation 17th chapter that got
the 10 horns okay that's dealing with
the uh European common market Mar let's
go read that Revelation 17 read verse 1
5 you get it go ahead and there came one
of the Seven Angels which had the seven
vows and talked with me saying unto me
come hither I will show unto thee the
Judgment of the great that sth
upon many Waters with whom the kings of
the Earth have committed
fornication and the inhab evidence of
the Earth had been made drunk with the
wine of her
fornication so he carried me away in the
spirit Into the Wilderness and I saw a
woman sit upon a Scarlet colored Beast
full of names of blasphemy having seven
heads and 10 horns and the woman was
arrayed in purple and scarlet color and
decked with gold and precious stones and
Pearls having a golden cup in her hand
full of Abominations and filthiness of
her fornication and upon her forehead
was a name written mystery Babylon the
great the mother of harlots and
Abominations of the Earth yeah so the
the woman that's uh she arrayed in
purple and scarlet color you know that's
that's the Catholic church over there in
Vatican City and uh the 10 horns that
was on that Beast is the European common
market which is over there in Western
Europe right now that's about that's
your uh mystery
Babylon that's all I got
on all right thank you for that hope
that answered your question as we keep
moving yes Zion asked for you to explain
John 11 verse 9 when Jesus said are
there not 12 hours in the day so is a
day Su down to Sun up averaging about 12
hours all right why don't we go to John
11 verse
9 and let's cut up these 24 hours 12 and
12 and the guest caller would take it
from there go ahead brother
James Jesus answered are there not 12
hours in the day if any man walk in the
day he stumbleth not because he seeth
the light of this
world the first thing is we want to show
you what a day consist
of let's go into Genesis the 1 chapter
read verses
1-5 Genesis 1 verse
1-5 in the beginning God created the
Heaven and the Earth and the Earth was
without form and void and darkness was
upon the face of the deep and the spirit
of God moved upon the face of the waters
and God said let there be light and
there was light and God saw the light
that it was good and God divided the
light from the darkness and God called
the light day and the Darkness he called
night and the evening and the morning
were the first
day okay so a day cons uh uh uh consist
of 24 hours
there's a time when the in the year when
the daylight is 12 hours and the dark is
12 hours so Jesus was saying he's
talking about in the day that's why I
said why you can see in those days you
didn't have all these big spotlights and
cars with with with with headlights on
and all big things that light up the
field when you have night baseball game
they had only candles so if you want to
see good why it was in the daytime at
night you just couldn't so Jesus was
talking about the daytime the part that
Genesis this first chapter called light
that's why it said a day the light he
called day for 24
hours real black real light that's all I
have to say all right hope that answered
your question is we keep moving to our
next one yes little mama Hayes asked
what is CERN CR n
CN and is this something that we should
be concerned about brother
Dre yeah um CERN is some some uh big
machine they built in Switzerland they
got others in different places but it's
it's supposed to be in search of what
they call the God particle and
it's a scientific thing and and and it
brings forth black holes and different
things of that nature but in terms of us
being concerned about whatever
inventions are searching out or whatever
somebody is doing let's go to in in
terms of Weaponry against you know God
let's go to Isaiah 54 Isaiah 54 and we
going to pick it up at verse 15 to 17 so
I don't think you should worry about
anything in terms of that as long as you
on the side of God and obedient to his
word that's right brother read that when
you get it start at verse
15 behold they shall surely gather
together but not by me whosoever Shall
Gather together against thee shall fall
for thy
sake behold I have created the Smith
that bloweth the coals and the fire and
that bringeth forth an instrument for
his work and I have created the waster
to
destroy no weapon that is formed against
thee shall prosper and every tongue that
shall rise against thee in judgment Thou
shalt condemn this is the heritage of
the Servants of the Lord and their
righteousness is of me saeth the Lord so
if we are in the righteousness of the
lord we standing on his word and
obedient to his way when that time comes
for us to go where we go when we see the
abomination of desolation and it's time
to flee don't waste time just be
obedient to God and these weapons that
are formed against you will not prosper
and if they do endure and to the end I
hope that that
helps brother um Dre I wanted to if I
may add Proverbs 8 yes sir verse 12 and
13 yes
sir Proverbs 8 verse 12 and 13 yes
sir
okay I wisdom dwell with with prudence
and find out knowledge of witty
inventions
the fear of the Lord is to hate evil
pride and arrogancy and and the evil way
and the forward mouth do I hate yeah so
just like brother Dre was saying all
them witty inventiones that they that
that's created the Lord know about them
you know but what we need to be worried
about is not doing evil and pleasing the
god of the creation which is Jesus
Christ that's all all right thank you
Brothers for that
explanation and um and we ask to that in
the future if you could please keep your
questions to things that pertain to the
King James Bible we'd appreciate that
very much all right next question sister
next question the real Miss Pebbles ask
in court should women cover their heads
Jerome should women cover their heads
and
Court well the the Bible tells us if if
you woman if you praying and prophesying
your head shall be covered it don't
matter where you at it's just if you
praying and prophesying that's when you
should have your head covered so if you
going to do that in court have your head
covered if you GNA pray or prophesy uh
the verse is uh 1 Corinthians the 11th
chapter uh verse four and
five all right that's right brother
Jerome did you want me to read that
yeah you should read
it first Corinthians where Corinthians
11 verse four and five all
right every man praying or prophesying
having his head covered dishonor his
head but every woman that prayeth or
prophesieth with her head uncovered
dishonor her head for that is even all
one as if she were shaven yeah that's
all I got all right thank you all for
that and uh just wanted to say since
they timeing about court brother Jerome
when you go in there you don't have to
swear when they ask you to raise your
hand you can always just affirm because
the Lord say that we need not
swear all right next question sister
next question Malik Shakur says in job 7
verse 20 job said he had sinned what was
his sin I thought he was a righteous man
second question who was he speaking to
in verse 21 God or his friend all right
let's go to job 7 and
20 job 7 and
20 job had
sin and what was his sin according to
this question read verse 20 brother and
the guess caller take it from
there I have sinned what shall I do unto
thee Oh thou preserver of men why H has
thou set me as a mark against thee so
that I am a burden to
myself and why doest thou not pardon my
transgression and take away my iniquity
for now shall I sleep in the dust and
thou shalt seek me in the morning but I
shall not be
I skip down and read verse
12 am I a sea or a whale that thou set
us a watch over
me now I want to show you something here
see job uh uh uh job was in the uh
really really being Afflicted okay
yep now skip down to verse 21 I I I'm
sorry I should have said verse 21 and
not 12 verse 21 read it and why doest
thou not pardon my transgression and
take away my iniquity for now shall I
sleep in the dust and thou shalt seek me
in the morning but I shall not
be okay first thing is
uh let's see what God said about job
okay
one 1 and verse
8 1 and
8 and the Lord said unto Satan has thou
considered my servant joob that there is
none like him in the earth a perfect and
unright upright man one that fearth God
and asseth
Evil now you read that and it said job
say he sin then God didn't know what he
was talking about but we know better
sometime when you inflict when you
Afflicted I mean really Afflicted you
say things that you should not say and
and uh job 6 we going to go to job 6 and
read verse 25 and
okay how forcible are right words but
what doth your arguing we
reprove do ye imagine to reprove words
and the speeches of one that is
desperate which are as
wind Jo was desperate the man you know
he lost all his kids night lost his help
he got BS and scars all over and he have
to get uh uh uh scat object and scrap
the SWS on him this man was in pain and
he was in desperate so he said do you
seek to uh uh uh uh you know to in other
words uh uh uh holding words against a
man that's in that's Afflicted his words
just like the
wind so Jo was sick everything going
with him he fig he must be in sin
somewhere even though I say it but uh
that six that 26 verse said it all read
that 26 verse again do ye imagine to
reprove words and the speeches of one
that is desperate which are as wind
do that speak for itself amen des and
and I mean and really painful and his
friends
there came down to comfor him but they
outright condemned him made feel fig you
must have did something yeah and these
were his friends that was talking let's
let's now let's go to
job 32 and read verses 1
through3 because the young man weighed
in on this thing because he saw how them
old friends of joob condemn him for no
reason read it when you get there so
these three men ceased to answer joob
because he was righteous in his own eyes
then was kindled the Wrath of elu the
son of barel the buzite of the Kindred
of Ram against job was his wrath kindled
because he justified himself rather than
God also against his three friends was
his wrath kindled because they had found
no answers and yet had condemned Jo yeah
so he was talking to his friend you know
you guys here and you accuse me of this
and accuse me of that in fact they
forced job to talk out his head
mhm that's why why it said in that and
uh uh uh it said you know that can can
you uh uh take serious or hold a man's
word against him who is
desperate his words are just like the wi
they mean nothing God called him
righteous and upright then he was a
righteous and upright man and he made
that statement he was a righteous and
upright man that was in D
Affliction and had some friend that's
condemning
him but
nothing yeah that's all yep and even the
Lord was upset with his
friends that's it J had to go pray for
him y oh
did all right we hope that answered your
question as we continue to move with the
time Check Yes moving on and the time is
6:20 uh Stephen googus asked are there
requirement are
require ah yes the time is
8:20 Stephen gugas asked are there
requirements for paying
offerings I know there is tithes which
is one1 or 10% of increase in Malachi 3
verse1 but what about
offerings all right so they understand
you got to pay 10% of your increase to
the tax but they want to know about
offering in that Malachi let's go there
brother James and open it up to the
panel let's go to that
Malachi and when you get there brother
read that verse 10 and let's see what it
says about
aring bring ye all the tides into the
storehouse that there may be meat in
mine house and prove me now herewith
sayeth the Lord of hosts if I will not
open you the windows of heaven and pour
you out a blessing that there shall not
be room enough to receive it all right
now notice notice he didn't say nothing
about offering didn't it no it says that
is a commandment ver for offering
offering is concerned let's go to
Leviticus the 22nd chapter yes sir and
read
17-9
okay Leviticus
17-9 and the Lord spake unto Moses
saying Speak unto Aaron and to his sons
and unto all the children of Israel and
say unto them whatsoever he be of the
House of Israel or of the strangers of
Israel that will offer his oblation for
for all his vows and for all his Free
Will offerings which they will offer
unto the Lord for a burnt offering ye
shall offer it you I'm sorry ye shall
offer at your own will a male without
blemish of the bees or of the sheep or
of the
goats now now read that verse again a
little better okay ye
shall ye shall offer at your own will a
man with a male without blemish of the
beaves of the sheep or of the
goats okay he said you should
offer you know of your own will only
time you obligated to do a free will
offering is if you vow it if you vow the
Lord I'm going put uh uh
$500 in CL in class today then if you
don't do it then you're in
violation but if you don't make the vow
you don't have to make no offering
that's why it's always called Free Will
offering you offering at your own will
only thing that the law requires is you
pay TI that ain't no free will that is a
commandment so no you don't have to pay
offer free will unless you vow to do it
that's all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
moving on Marcia Samuel says if you are
called to pray for the members of the
church should you be calling upon daddy
example Daddy I call upon you to bless
this church and heal us the person said
God is I am which is any name
brother Julius is what you
got wow the churches have gone away from
the word of God and they lean to their
own understanding and they want to bring
in cliches because they think it means
something let's look at what the Lord
said Matthew the 6th
chapter Matthew the 6th chapter I have
people comeing to me Daddy I'm praying
to my dad I'm praying to my dad I'm
praying I understand what you're saying
but let's look at what the book say
Matthew
6 and pick it and read one
verse Matthew 6
and9 after this manner therefore pray ye
Our Father which art in heaven Hallowed
be thy name our
daddy our father just do like the book
say just do like the book said that's
all I got
Corel all right r
God is Holy and he's a SP spirit and
they that worship Him must worship Him
in spirit and in truth and you do it
with reverence and
respect that's all I
got all
right hope that answered your question
as we keep moving sister Deborah are we
going into new
territory uh yes we are now into
tonight's Q&A for July the 24th
2024 Malik Shakur
says my son's friend is 25 years old and
teaches on the Sabbath is there a
scripture I can show him that you have
to be at least 30 to teach I know he
will then hit me
with Acts 2 verse
17 can you
explain all right acts
2:7 when you get there brother pick it
up and then the guest caller we weigh in
there about this 25 year old that's
teaching on the
Sabbath and it shall come to pass in the
last days sayith God I will pour out of
my spirit upon All Flesh and your sons
and your daughter daughter shall
prophesy and your young men shall see
visions and your old men shall dream
dreams now that didn't say anything
about uh uh him
teaching woman can prophesy The Bu was a
prophet that mean that you can give a
message that God give you a message but
this is not talking about you can come
into the ministry you can read that all
you want without uh uh under 30 now
let's go into numbers the fourth
chapter we're going to read one and
three then we're going to skip we're
going to make two or three skips numbers
1-3 and the Lord spake unto Moses and
unto Aaron saying take the sum of the
sons of koho from among the sons of Levi
after their families by the house of
their fathers from 30 years old and
upward even un 50 years old all that
enter into the host to do the work in
the Tabernacle of the
congregation now skip down to verse
20 let's
see get down to verse 23 and read it
from 30 years old and upward until until
50 years old shalt thou number them all
that enter in to perform the service to
do the work in the Tabernacle of the
congregation verse
30 from 30 years old and upward even
unto 50 years old shalt thou number them
everyone that entereth into the service
service to do the work of the Tabernacle
of the congregation
now the word we're using here is that
really stands out is to
everyone everyone and Skip now to verse
43 and read
it from 30 years old and upward even
until 50 years old everyone that
entereth into the service for the work
in the Tabernacle of the
congregation so now that is the law that
is the law the Lord set it up if you
going to enter into the ministry you got
to be 30 years uh and if you're 50 years
you're too old if you know uh uh uh and
uh if you 51 years old you're too old
because he's from 30 to 50 now this is
so strong until Jesus adhere to it when
Jesus show you that he didn't have no uh
uh limitation on understanding he stayed
behind one time after they kept some
feast days and his mother and father was
looking for him and they found him and
what was he doing he was in standing
among the elders and he was asking them
question and answering their question at
12 years old but he could not start the
ministry because of the law now let's so
go and see what he start when he started
this ministry let's go into Luke the 3
chapter we're going to read verse 21 to
now when all the people were baptized it
came to pass that Jesus also being
baptized and praying the heaven was open
and the Holy Ghost descended in a bodily
shape like a dove upon him and a voice
Came From Heaven which said Thou Art my
beloved Son in thee I am well pleased
and
Jesus now that's when Jesus was anointed
when he come up out of that
go ahead finish it go ahead and Jesus
himself began to be about 30 years of
age being as was supposed the son of
Joseph which was the son of
Hilo now Jesus with all his knowledge
the Bible said the Lord didn't put no
limit on his
knowledge that's why he was able to dis
uh uh answer question of the elders and
and and ask them question
but the ministry because he could not
break the law it ain't no accident that
Jesus ministry started at 30 because it
is the law now whether this young guy
want to believe it or not that's up to
him but if he is St if he is tell
himself teaching even on the Sabbath at
25 years old he is breaking the
law that's all I have to say all right
hope that answered your question as we
move move on to the next one next one
Orlando Davy asks according to the
dietary law are mushrooms and seaweed
clean all right brother Jerome can we e
mushrooms and
seaweed well the dietary law you read
about in Leviticus 11th chapter it's
about what Beast we can and cannot eat
it's not about what about the
vegetation excuse me so let's go take a
look at it let's go to Leviticus the
11th chapter and read verse 1 and
two and the Lord spake unto Moses and to
Aaron saying unto them speak unto the
children of Israel saying these are the
beasts of which ye shall eat among all
the beasts that are on the
earth that's good so it's not talking
about the vegetation it's talking about
the beast that's the dietary law you
reading in this Leviticus chapter
11 that's all I got
on all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next and
brother Cornell the Lord told you in
Genesis he gave man every herb of the
field you
know that's correct is good yeah yep
there certain you can't eat some of them
certain mushroom you you you can't eat
they
poisonous that's right avoid that poison
ivy don't eat
that all right we hope that aned your
question as we move on to our next one
moving on Victor Holly asked was Paul
the last
Apostle yes carer was Paul the last
Apostle best answer for that is that
Paul came after the 12
apostles now was there somebody else
after him we don't
know but he came after the 12
apostles years
after that's the only answer I can give
you all right hope that answered your
question next
one next one I chuck woo Amar asks are
you supposed to pay Ties on any money
you get that is not from the work of
your hand
profession example land dispute
settlements gifts accident settlements
wheels from loved ones
Etc all right so do you have to pay
tithes on any money that is gifted in
your hand sounds like an increase guess
caller go
ahead yeah let's go to Deuteronomy 26
chapter and read verse 12
Deuteronomy
26 and
verse when thou has made an end of
tithing all the tithes of thine increase
the third year which is the year of
tithing and has given it unto the levite
the stranger the fatherless and the
Widow that they may eat within thy Gates
and be filled
now he the tithing of all your
increase let's go into Deuteronomy 14
read
22 and Skip down and read
28 thou sh Thou shalt thy tithe all the
increase of thy seed that thy field
bringeth forth year by
year and at the end of three years Thou
shalt bring forth all the tithe of thine
increase the same year and shall lay it
up within thy
Gates what verse was that that was
28 both of them said all thy increase
didn't it correct one last 2 Chronicles
31 and5
read it when you get there
okay and as soon as the Commandment came
abroad the children of Israel brought in
abundance the first fruits of corn wine
and oil and honey and all of the
increase of the field and the tithe of
all things brought they in
abundant so it is all you increase it
don't matter how it came to you if you
get it you owe the Lord 10% of it only
thing that the Lord don't want is the uh
price of of a prostitute or either the
price of a
sodomite that is if woman go out and
sell herself he don't want none of that
money thought might go uh get paid uh uh
somebody pay you for sodomizing them he
don't want that money but other than
that whatever your increase is what ever
come into your hand is an increase it's
something that you didn't have before it
came so you supposed to pay 10% of it
according to the scripture don't have to
say all right hope that answers your
question as we move on to the next yes
Deborah Davis wants you to provide her
with
scripture stating we should worship on
the
Sabbath well it's a lot of scriptures
that tell you that you should be
worshiping on the Sabbath let's go to
let's go to um Exodus 20 first brother
Exodus 20 we'll read a couple and then
we go move to another book Exodus
20 and this is why you worship on the
Sabbath too Exodus 20 pick it up verse
one go ahead we read this earlier by
Brother Julius go ahead and God spake
all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought the out of the land of Egypt out
of the house of bondage thou shal have
no other gods before me thou shal not
make unto thee any Graven image or any
brother that's good right there so I
just wanted to let it be known that thou
sh have no other God for me and when we
talking about wor worshiping on the
Sabbath day of course we're talking
about the seventh day of the week skip
down and read verse six for
me and showing Mercy unto thousand of
them that love me and keep my
Commandments that's a Commandment that
you are supposed to worship and honor
the Sabbath Day verse eight remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy all right
turn over brother Leviticus 23 right
quick Leviticus the 23rd
chapter and when you get
there pick it up at that verse one and
then we go skip down to verse three go
right ahead
and the Lord spake unto Moses saying
53 six days shal work be done but the
seventh day is the Sabbath of rest and
holy
convocation ye shall do no work therein
it is the Sabbath of the Lord in all
your dwellings so the L same Lord we
read about that Exodus 20 is giving
Moses right here instructions in this
Leviticus that six days you can work but
on the seventh day you supposed to rest
and have a holy conversation get
together with other brothers and sisters
that are keeping the Sabbath day turn
over to Isaiah
56 Isaiah
56 when you get there brother read one
and
two one and
two thus sayeth the Lord keep ye
judgment and do justice for my salvation
is near to come and my righteousness to
be revealed
soon blessed is the man that doeth this
and the son of man that layeth hold on
it that keepeth the Sabbath from
polluting it and keepeth his hand from
doing any evil now turn over to Isaiah
58 and then this should be last of it
right Isaiah 58 read 13 and 14 cuz the
Lord said this is a holy day you're
supposed to be glad to have the
knowledge of partaken in it and you're
supposed to respect it go ahead if thou
turn away thy foot from the Sabbath from
doing thy pleasure on my holy day and
call the Sabbath a delight the holy of
the Lord honorable and shall honor him
not doing thine own ways nor finding
thine own pleasure nor speaking thine
own
words then in shalt thou Delight thyself
in the Lord and I will cause thee to
ride upon the high places of the earth
and feed thee with the heritage of Jacob
thy father for the mouth of the Lord has
spoken it that's right do all according
to what the Lord say and hey you'll even
get eternal life but the Lord say this
is a holy day his day and he want all of
his servants and children to honor it
that's all I got and Luke the 4th
chapter verse 16 he said as Jesus custom
was he went in his synagogue on the
Sabbath
day all right yes sir hope that answered
your question next
one yes M OG ask in the first
resurrection when the saints meet Jesus
in the air does this mean they are being
a wave offering to the Father Like Jesus
was at his his resurrection before they
return to the Mount of
Olives yes Cara what you
say no that's not when they being wave
up offer I want to show you something
here let's uh uh uh first then let's
let's look at these Saints that's coming
back go to Zechariah the 14th chapter I
read
45 Zechariah 14
and read four and five when you get
there
brother and his feet shall stand in that
day upon the Mount of Olives which is
before Jerusalem on the East and the
Mount of Olives shall cleave in the
midst thereof toward the East and toward
the west and there shall be a very great
valley and half of the mountain shall
remove toward the North and half of it
toward the South and ye shall flee to
the Valley of the mountains for the
Valley of the mountains shall reach unto
AEL yay ye shall flee like as ye fled
from before the earthquake in the days
of Uzziah king of Judah and the Lord my
God shall come and all the saints with
thee now these are the guys that the
Saints of the people that's going to
meet him in the air first Thessalonians
the 4th chapter talks about but they
have not been offered let me show you
why I know that let's go into Leviticus
the 23rd chapter read uh from 10 to 12
Leviticus 2310
to2 speak unto the children of Israel
and say unto them when ye be come into
the land which I give unto you and shall
reap the Harvest thereof then ye shall
bring a sheath of the first fruit of
your Harvest unto the priest and he
shall wave the sheath before the Lord to
be accepted for you on the tomorrow
after the Sabbath the priest shall wave
it now pay attention it say the marrow
after the
Sabbath the priest shall wave it if you
read further it'll tell you about it'll
tell you about uh in fact
let's look at the
uh but that's enough tomorrow after the
Sabbath that's the first fruit now God
gave man one week seven
days now all the time uh for that seven
days you got Flesh and Blood people here
so now that offering include the people
in the first resurrection and in the
last Resurrection now once they over
with then they then then they will be
offered up to God that's and uh let's go
into First Corinthians 15 and start
reading at verse
21 15 and 21
start for since man for Since By Man
Came Death by man came also the
resurrection of the Dead for as in Adam
all die even so in Christ shall all be
made
alive goe but every man in his own order
Christ the first fruits afterward they
that are Christ at his
coming then cometh oh I'm
sorry okay that's after it's coming and
and when it's coming then he going to
have to rule rule this Earth for a
thousand years and that's the seventh
day when his rulership stop then let's
see what he going to do keep reading
then cometh the end when he shall have
delivered up the kingdom to God even the
father when he shall have put down all
Rule and all authority and
power for he must rain oh I'm sorry go
ahead for he must Reign till he hath put
all enemies under his
feet The Last Enemy that shall be
destroyed is
death now so Jesus got to come the
people going to meet him in the first
resurrection he going to rule his Earth
for a thousand years and at the end of
the Thousand at the end of the Thousand
Years you know I'm talking a part of the
Thousand Years that gets to the end he
going to have the white Throne judgment
and all the people that's going to make
it
just like the people in the first
resurrection going to make it they all
change because he going to terminate
death so they all going to be Immortals
then he going to offer up them to the
father on the eth day because the
father's Kingdom don't come until the
eth day and you find that Kingdom in in
Revelation the 21st chapter so when he
offer up the create you cannot offer up
the fruit to
God on the seventh day
it can only be done on the eth day which
is the first day of
the
okay
yep all
right all right hope that answers your
question is we move on to our next
question yes moving on just W uh just
looking as you to
explain 1 Corinthians 12 verse3 and
Romans 8 verse three all right um
brother Jerome can you um expound on
that 1 Corinthians 12
and3 yeah let's go take a look at it um
brother James when you get it go ahead
and
read wherefore I give you to understand
that no man speaking by the spirit of
God calleth Jesus a curse and that no
man can say that Jesus is the Lord but
by the Holy
Ghost
okay so it said wherefore I give you to
understand that no man speaketh by the
spirit of God Called Jesus a curse and
that no man can say that Jesus is the
Lord but by the Holy Ghost it's by the
word of God that we
understand who the true and living God
is even Jesus Christ cuz they got
another Jesus that's not the Jesus of
this Bible he the Jesus of Sunday he the
Jesus of Easter and Christmas but the
ones
that's got the Holy Spirit the word of
God they know that the Jesus of this
Bible is the Jesus of the Passover and
we call him the Christ that other one he
not the Christ you know
uh but that's that 1 Corinthians 12 and
13 uh 12 and 3 right correct yeah yeah
that that's that's all I got on there if
anybody want to add something that can
all right let show
you let's show you what that spirit of
God and that Holy Ghost is okay go to 6
chapter and read verse
63 what chapter again brother Bo you
know Sor guess
caller St John chapter
6 thanks a lot sorry
sir 6 and uh chapter 6 and verse 63
it is the spirit that quickeneth the
flesh profiteth nothing the words that I
speak unto you they are spirit and they
are
life so if you don't know the word of
God
then you you you you could say what the
uh uh what we just said you have to know
what that spirit is and the Holy Ghost
it is the word of God that's all I have
to say
all
right okay we hope that answered your
question and now the second part of that
question at Romans 8 and3 brother Julius
is what you got let's go read that
brother James Romans 8
and3 for what the law could not do and
that it was weak through the flesh God
sending his his own son in the likeness
of sinful flesh and for sin condemn
condemned sin in the the flesh first
John 3:4 says that sin is the
transgression of the law this is not
this is that's the Royal that's the Ten
Commandments this right here for what
the law could not do that was animal
sacrifice so the blood of let's read
that let's go to Hebrews the n9th
chapter Hebrews chapter
n and when you get it brother James we
going to read 12- 14 Hebrews 9 12-4
I'm sorry stay down right there Hebrews
10 and 4 first Hebrews 10 and 4 and then
we'll back up Hebrews 10 and 4 when you
get it brother what it say for it is not
possible that the blood of bulls and of
goats should take away sins
because the animal didn't sin man did so
that was the law the lord gave you
animal sacrifice to cover your sin and
make an atonement for your sins and
until he came it was never possible he
never wanted that for the bull for it is
not possible that the blood of bulls and
goat should take away sin back up and
let's look at what can take away sin
Hebrews the nth chapter and we gonna
read verses 12-
14 when you get it go ahead Hebrews 9 12
and 14 well pick it up at 11 let's look
at who we talking about go ahead but
Christ being come and high priest of
good things to come by a greater and
more perfect Tabernacle not made with
hands that is to say not of this
building go ahead neither by the blood
of goats and calves but by his own blood
he entered in once into the holy Place
having obtained Eternal Redemption for
us how did he do that read it for if the
blood of bulls and of goats and the
ashes of an hepher sprinkling the
unclean
sanctifieth to the purifying of the
flesh how much how much more shall the
blood of Christ who through the eternal
spirit offered himself without spot to
God purge yourself Purge your conscience
from dead Works to serve the Living God
and that's why when Christ died on the
cross and shed his blood the book says
the be was written in Twain that end and
animal sacrifice CU it was never
possible for the blood of and go to take
away sin so Christ had to come shed his
blood make an atonement for us all and
that's why Isaiah said by his stripes we
are healed now you got to hide up under
the blood the shed blood of Jesus I hope
that
helps let me something yes call go to
Hebrews the 10th chapter and read verse
one this is the law that was weak I
wanted to call it by name go ahead for
the law having a shadow of good things
to come and not the very image of the
things can never with those sacrifices
which they offered year by year
continually make the comers there un
unto
perfect I just want you to make you know
that there was more than one law that's
named so this law was the law of animal
sacrifice it couldn't do what Jesus
because it was weak in the flesh that's
why Jesus had to come In the Flesh
that's why it said in four in in the
fifth 10 and five a body thou Hast
prepared
me that's yes sir that's right yep and
like you say Jerome how could be how
could he be a curse and he was a Holy
One of
Israel all right let's keep it moving
sister Deborah next question yes Sandra
hering says he needs some clarification
on Leviticus 10 verse 6 uncover not your
heads Leviticus 10 and 6 uncover not
your heads let's go there brother James
when you get there read that Leviticus
10 and6 guess caller take it from
there and
six and Moses said unto Aaron and unto
Eleazar and unto ethar his sons uncover
not your heads neither Ren your your
clothes least you die and least wrath
come upon all the people but let your
brethren the whole house of Israel
bewell the burning which the Lord has
kindled oh it mean what it said don't
uncover your head because the priest had
a job to do and when they went inside
the Tabernacle they had special uh uh
garments they put on what them with
bonage that they woke and what happened
was they was grieving because their
brother had been killed back up to the
first verse and start reading Leviticus
And1 and naab and abue the sons of Aaron
took either of them his sensor and put
fire therein and put incense thereon and
offer Strange Fire before the Lord which
he commanded them not
go and there went out out fire from the
Lord and devoured them and they died
before the
Lord now what happened was these are
these guys two older brothers God killed
them he said look I don't want you
taking off your bunny and going out
among the people grieving and and uh uh
uh and and uh uh mourning for these
brothers you know because they did wrong
and I kill them you'll be about your
work so if you take off your Bonnet your
covering of your head and go grieving
for them I'm going to kill you too but
mean what he said do not uncover your
head that's all I have to say all right
hope that answered your question next
question next question night like
crawler ask do the seven begin when the
Sun is up or at night in the scripture
given are Jeremiah 17 vers 19-
22 and John 11 verses 9 through
16 all right well do the Sabbath begin
when the Sun is up or at night well it
begins at night so does every new day
and that Jeremiah 17 that you got 19- 22
it doesn't even jail with that question
that you ask let's go there quickly
the Jeremiah
17 and
19 go ahead when you get it
brother thus sayith the Lord unto me go
and stand in the gate of the children of
the people whereby the kings of Judah
come in and by the which they go out and
in all the Gates of Jerusalem all right
skip down to verse 22 because uh this
doesn't have anything to do with uh the
Sabbath again 22 go ahead neither carry
forth a burden out of your houses on the
Sabbath day neither do ye any work but
Hollow ye the Sabbath day as I commanded
your fathers all right it just mentions
the Sabbath day but not when it begins
or end and the same thing applies to
that John 11 and that verse 9-16 so for
time sake we're not going to read that
we're going to go straight and let you
know when the Sabbath begins turn back
to Genesis 1 Genesis
1 because sometime you may submit a
question and doesn't have anything to do
with what you asked here so we're going
to bypass that uh Genesis 1 we already
read 1-5 earlier by the guest callers
let's just pick it up at verse five
because we know it was Darkness the Lord
brought in light verse five and God
called the light day and the darkness he
called night and the evening and the
morning were the first day so you got to
have a evening which is the beginning of
night that's the definition of evening
it is the beginning of night and then
that brought in a day a new day Skip
down brother verse
eight and God called called the
firmament Heaven and the evening the
morning was the second day so we brought
in another day by having evening first
and then morning verse
13 and the evening and the morning were
the third day same thing applies to that
you have to have an evening which is
night which is the beginning of night
verse 19 go ahead and the evening in the
morning was the fourth day and last one
brother read that verse 23 you got to
have an evening first to bring in a New
Day verse 23 go ahead and the evening
and the morning were the fifth day the
Lord keep telling us the evening and the
morning let's see what job say this will
be the last one job turn over to job
because job lets us know here that in
order for evening got to to be gone you
have to have light brought in you can
have light and
dark on the same time schedule here job
7 and read 1 verse4 what did job say
when he lie down
James when I lie down down I say when
shall I arise and the night be gone and
I am full of tossings to and fro until
the dawning of the day oh so night is
not gone until you have the light and
the dawning of the day coming in now you
getting rid of night which is also
evening and I think people have a
problem with that word evening which is
the beginning of Night and the Sabbath
don't begin when the sun go down because
when the sun set if you look to the West
you got a whole lot of light still left
so it's not brought in the Sabbath day
yet it has to be dark in order for the
Sabbath to come in and that's all I got
Cornell can we read that dark part what
it means in Proverbs 7 and N yes sir
let's go there Proverbs 7
and9 okay
go ahead brother in the Twilight in the
evening in the black and dark night
because that's when the evening starts
in the black and dark night yes sir
thank you for that ad on there brother
and uh we hope that answered their
question and sister Deborah as we do a
Time
Check Yes the time is
9:02 uhoh we didn't ran Straight Out of
Time
want to thank everybody who tuned in
with us this evening and sent in all
those questions we had joy in answering
them for you but if you submitted a
question we didn't have time to get to
it please don't resubmit sister
Deborah's going to take it put it in
rotation and we will deal with your
question next week at the same time so
until we all come together again we ask
that you all be safe out there be
blessed and may the Lord have mercy on
us all as brother James closes
herself Our Father which art in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our debts as we forgive
our debtors and lead us not into
temptation but Deliver Us from Evil for
thine is the kingdom and the power and
the glory forever in Jesus name we pray
amen amen amen